<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Martin Kubečka</title>
    <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Martin Kubečka</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://martinkubecka.sk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Self Hosting News Aggregator</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/posts/news_aggregator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/posts/news_aggregator/</guid>
      <description>Enhance your digital privacy with self-hosted news aggregator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Your Own Recursive DNS Server</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/posts/resursive_dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/posts/resursive_dns/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to set up your own Recursive DNS Server at home on a Raspberry Pi 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weaponizing Malicious Macros</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/posts/malicious-macros/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/posts/malicious-macros/</guid>
      <description>Learn about crafting and analyzing Microsoft Excel malicious macros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Cybersecurity Analyst with main interest in Cyber Defense, Cyber Threat Intelligence, Open-Source Intelligence Techniques and Social Engineering. I completed my Master&amp;rsquo;s degree at the Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Information Technology of the Slovak University of Technology in Bratislava, where I pursued Computer Science with a focus on the security of information technologies.
In my spare time, I make the Internet a safer place by reporting application and system vulnerabilities to local and foreign companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Library</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/library/</guid>
      <description>My Latest Reading List #17 : How to Hack Like a Legend  Subtitle: Breaking Windows Author: Sparc Flow Publication Date: October 25, 2022 Length: 216 pages ISBN: 9781718501508 Publisher: No Starch Press  #16 : Practical Vulnerability Management  Subtitle: A Strategic Approach to Managing Cyber Risk Author: Andrew Magnusson Publication Date: September 29, 2020 Length: 192 pages ISBN: 9781593279882 Publisher: No Starch Press  #15 : Intrusion Detection Honeypots  Subtitle: Detection through Deception Author: Chris Sanders Publish Date: September 11, 2020 Length: 238 pages ISBN: 9781735188300 Publisher: Applied Network Defense  #14 : Cyber Warfare  Subtitle: Truth, Tactics, and Strategies Author: Chase Cunningham Publication Date: February 25, 2020 Length: 330 pages ISBN: 9781839216992 Publisher: Packt  #13 : The Art of Cyberwarfare  Subtitle: An Investigator&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Espionage, Ransomware, and Organized Cybercrime Author: Jon DiMaggio Publication Date: April 26, 2022 Length: 272 pages ISBN: 9781718502147 Publisher: No Starch Press  #12 : How to Hack Like a Ghost  Subtitle: Breaching the Cloud Author: Sparc Flow Publication Date: May 3, 2021 Length: 264 pages ISBN: 9781718501263 Publisher: No Starch Press  #11 : Sandworm  Subtitle: A New Era of Cyberwar and the Hunt for the Kremlin&amp;rsquo;s Most Dangerous Hackers Author: Andy Greenberg Publication Date: November 5, 2019 Length: 348 pages ISBN: 0385544405 Publisher: Doubleday  #10 : The Art of Deception  Subtitle: Controlling the Human Element of Security Author: Kevin D.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
