<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Martin Kubečka</title>
    <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Martin Kubečka</description>
    <image>
      <title>Martin Kubečka</title>
      <url>https://martinkubecka.sk/images/avatar_transparent.png</url>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/images/avatar_transparent.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://martinkubecka.sk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unsofisticating Phishing Delivering Sofistiacted Malware</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/posts/2025-10-02-unsofisticating-phishing-delivering-sofistiacted-malware/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/posts/2025-10-02-unsofisticating-phishing-delivering-sofistiacted-malware/</guid>
      <description>Deep dive analysis of an opportunistic phishing campaign delivering Katz Stealer and Remcos RAT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-56683: DOM-based Cross-Site Scripting Leading to Remote Code Execution in Logseq Application</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/security-advisories/cve-2025-56683/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/security-advisories/cve-2025-56683/</guid>
      <description>A DOM-based XSS vulnerability in Logseq version 0.10.9 allows Remote Code Execution by injecting malicious JavaScript through unsanitized plugin README content combined with insufficient protocol validation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2023-47622: Multiple Reflected Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerabilities in IT Service Management Platform iTop</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/security-advisories/cve-2023-47622/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/security-advisories/cve-2023-47622/</guid>
      <description>Reflected XSS vulnerability in multiple query parameters of Combodo iTop’s render endpoint allows JavaScript injection and execution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Cybersecurity Analyst with main interest in Cyber Defense, Cyber Threat Intelligence, Open-Source Intelligence Techniques and Social Engineering. I completed my Master&amp;rsquo;s degree at the Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Information Technology of the Slovak University of Technology in Bratislava, where I pursued Computer Science with a focus on the security of information technologies.
In my spare time, I make the Internet a safer place by reporting application and system vulnerabilities to local and foreign companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Latest Reading List</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/library/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/library/</guid>
      <description>#21 : Evading EDR Subtitle: The Definitive Guide to Defeating Endpoint Detection Systems Author: Matt Hand Publication Date: September, 2023 Length: 312 Pages ISBN: 9781718503342 Publisher: No Starch Press #20 : Intelligence-Driven Incident Response Subtitle: Outwitting the Adversary, 2nd Edition Author: Rebekah Brown, Scott Roberts Publication Date: June, 2023 Length: 316 Pages ISBN: 9781098120689 Publisher: O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media, Inc. #19 : We Are Bellingcat Subtitle: An Intelligence Agency for the People Author: Eliot Higgins Publication Date: March, 2021 Length: 272 Pages ISBN: 9781635577303 Publisher: Bloomsbury Publishing Inc #18 : Advanced Penetration Testing Subtitle: Hacking the World&amp;rsquo;s Most Secure Networks Author: Wil Allsopp Publication Date: February, 2017 Length: 288 Pages ISBN: 9781119367680 Publisher: Wiley #17 : How to Hack Like a Legend Subtitle: Breaking Windows Author: Sparc Flow Publication Date: October, 2022 Length: 216 Pages ISBN: 9781718501508 Publisher: No Starch Press #16 : Practical Vulnerability Management Subtitle: A Strategic Approach to Managing Cyber Risk Author: Andrew Magnusson Publication Date: September, 2020 Length: 192 Pages ISBN: 9781593279882 Publisher: No Starch Press #15 : Intrusion Detection Honeypots Subtitle: Detection through Deception Author: Chris Sanders Publish Date: September, 2020 Length: 238 Pages ISBN: 9781735188300 Publisher: Applied Network Defense #14 : Cyber Warfare Subtitle: Truth, Tactics, and Strategies Author: Chase Cunningham Publication Date: February, 2020 Length: 330 Pages ISBN: 9781839216992 Publisher: Packt #13 : The Art of Cyberwarfare Subtitle: An Investigator&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Espionage, Ransomware, and Organized Cybercrime Author: Jon DiMaggio Publication Date: April, 2022 Length: 272 Pages ISBN: 9781718502147 Publisher: No Starch Press #12 : How to Hack Like a Ghost Subtitle: Breaching the Cloud Author: Sparc Flow Publication Date: May, 2021 Length: 264 Pages ISBN: 9781718501263 Publisher: No Starch Press #11 : Sandworm Subtitle: A New Era of Cyberwar and the Hunt for the Kremlin&amp;rsquo;s Most Dangerous Hackers Author: Andy Greenberg Publication Date: November, 2019 Length: 348 Pages ISBN: 0385544405 Publisher: Doubleday #10 : The Art of Deception Subtitle: Controlling the Human Element of Security Author: Kevin D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Hosting News Aggregator</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/posts/2023-09-23-news-aggregator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/posts/2023-09-23-news-aggregator/</guid>
      <description>Enhance your digital privacy with self-hosted news aggregator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41433: Authentication Bypass in Resumes Management by EGavilan Media</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/security-advisories/cve-2021-41433/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/security-advisories/cve-2021-41433/</guid>
      <description>SQL injection vulnerability in EGavilan Media&amp;#39;s Resumes Management and Job application allows unauthenticated attackers to bypass login authentication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41432: Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in the Blog Content in FlatPress</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/security-advisories/cve-2021-41432/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/security-advisories/cve-2021-41432/</guid>
      <description>Stored XSS vulnerability in FlatPress 1.2.1 allows arbitrary JavaScript execution via crafted post content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-41434: Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in Expense Management System by EGavilan Media</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/security-advisories/cve-2021-41434/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/security-advisories/cve-2021-41434/</guid>
      <description>Stored XSS vulnerability in Expense Management System 1.0 allows arbitrary JavaScript execution via expense description input.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Your Own Recursive DNS Server</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/posts/2022-01-28-resursive-dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/posts/2022-01-28-resursive-dns/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to set up your own Recursive DNS Server at home on a Raspberry Pi 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2021-37413: Authentication Bypass in Content Management System Provided by GRANDCOM, s.r.o.</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/security-advisories/cve-2021-37413/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/security-advisories/cve-2021-37413/</guid>
      <description>Unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability in GRANDCOM CMS allows login bypass via crafted username.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weaponizing Malicious Macros</title>
      <link>https://martinkubecka.sk/posts/2021-05-12-malicious-macros/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinkubecka.sk/posts/2021-05-12-malicious-macros/</guid>
      <description>Learn about crafting and analyzing Microsoft Excel malicious macros.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
